In today’s episode,
we will be scaring you with some spooky Halloween festivities.
We’ll also be launching an unprecedented
experiment and introducing a new status effect.
Hello, tankers.
We missed you badly and are very happy to
see you all again.
First off,
Happy Halloween!
The festive mode is available on THREE maps,
which are selected randomly:
the Graveyard map in 2015 and 2016 versions and the Highland
map from 2013.
Who asked for old Tanki?
Here you are.
Enjoy!
Of course,
there will be an increased gold box chance,
as well as boosted funds and experience.
Plus,
we have prepared a lot of special missions.
As usual,
you can complete them only for a limited time,
but a couple of them will be available for
just one day.
However,
the prize will be special.
You will find more information in the official
announcement.
For those who’ve been waiting for sales,
we are pleased to announce that today,
we have a 30% discount on any item in the
Shop,
tomorrow everything in the garage will be
30% off,
and on Sunday,
you can micro-upgrade your new equipment at a 30% discount,
and speed up those upgrades at half the price.
Also, you will be able to get three Halloween special offers at once with “terrible” discounts.
Ultra Containers will return to the game for
the time of the celebration.
We'll tell you why they are important in just
a second.
Let's talk about Hornet's Overdrive.
We left the radar unchanged.
And the ability to ignore the enemy's resists
and armor has turned into a new status effect
Armor-Piercing
We changed the way the Hornets Overdrive works.
The Armor-Piercing effect is not a permanent
effect.
It can be applied only when you activate the
overdrive
and only on the opponents who are visible.
The duration of the effect will be shorter
than the duration of the overdrive itself.
Yes,the radius of the effect application is almost unlimited,
the only important factor is that the target must be visible.
Plus, the Armor-Piercing effect will be available
to your teammates as well.
On the other hand,
the Armor-Piercing effect is a status effect,
and you will be able to equip a special augment
on your hull to protect yourself against it.
It will allow players who understand the situation
on the battlefield better to stand out,
and those who played with minimal risk
will now lose the ability to easily make the most out of Hornet’s overdrive.
In addition to Hornet,
this status effect can be applied to some turrets
if you have the required augments. But there also will be differences.
For example,
a simple shot with Railgun will be enough to activate the Armor-Piercing effect,
but Ricochet, for example,
will have to hit the opponent with a ricochet from the wall to activate this effect.
In conclusion,
it will not be possible to give out the effect to everyone easily
you will have to try hard to obtain it.
You'll need to complete the Halloween special
missions to get them from Ultra Containers.
And yes, all of these new augments are already available in the Ultra Containers,
so if you don't want to wait to get your hands on them,
then try your luck by buying some right now!
Up next, we have an important topic
as it will bring some major changes.
From November 4th,
we will try a set of changes right in the game.
These changes are designed to increase the
importance of team gameplay
while trying not to change the dynamics of the battle.
This test will increase the amount of health
and the amount of charge for melee turrets such as Firebird or Isida.
We will remove larger maps from the Matchmaking
system and focus on 6 vs 6 gamemode
while reducing the length of the battle to 5 minutes.
If all goes as planned,
these changes will allow you to spend more time in the battle itself,
rather than spending time respawning.
The testing will last for 2 weeks.
We understand that most of the old players
will not like the changes.
However,
we ask you to play with it for a few days first,
and then, answer the following questions in the comments:
Do you think you had less deaths where you
spawned and were completely useless?
How did the benefit of well-timed overdrives
and drones change?
How did the importance of the team gameplay
change?
Could our experiment change your interest
in the game?
We thank you in advance.
This Halloween is surely a unique one.
Though we may not be able to go trick-or-treating
in person,
our reporters will ensure we'll all still
have a memorable day here in Tanki.
Just in time for the season,
the Newspaper has prepared a spooky Halloween special - complete with bone-chilling tales,
light and humorous holiday-themed articles,
and of course,
a handful of tricks and treats!
Dive into this seasonal issue right now; we
hope you enjoy it!
The link is in the description.
Anyway!
The eSports scene is actively growing in Tanki,
and there is a pretty good chance that you've read at least one of the many exciting
and engaging articles on our TankiSport site;
articles crafted by our incredible eSports
Reporters.
Very luckily for you,
the thriving eSports News team is now looking to expand with some new blood on their team.
Being an eSports Reporter is the perfect opportunity
to develop and grow your writing skills
while producing show-stopping articles,
all while gaining valuable English and eSports knowledge!
So if you think you're up for the job,
feel free to apply on the Volunteers Recruitment Portal via the link in the description below!
Psst...if you need some extra support on the
application,
we've also got a guide linked below,
just for you.
I'm sure they can't wait to welcome you into
their team!
We hid some secret codes in the past 4 episodes
of the V-LOG,
which you had to find and enter in a special
form.
When judging the results,
we took not only the correctness of the answer into account,
but also how fast you entered them.
You can see the list of the winners on your
screen.
The winners are also in the description.
Welcome back to Youtuber Digest,
our weekly selection of the best TO videos created by players.
Rank ups.
Everyone has them.
But watch Vision TO as he creates for us a
mega montage of rank ups!
Second,
watch Tanki Elite
as he creates a Gold Box montage titled 'Floating in Dreams'.
Quick reminder,
if you want to be featured in a future episode of the V-LOG,
then share your videos in the YouTuber Wannabe Form,
which can be found in the description.
That's all for this week.
We will see you next time.
But first,
leave a like,
subscribe,
hit the notification bell,
and watch until the Question of the Week.
And if you don’t leave a like,
you will have the same nightmare over and
over again one week long: everyone will be
using Juggernaut except you!
Bye!
Last time,
you had to guess which zone Ares would be destroyed in.
The correct answer is: С
Congratulations to the winners!
And here is the next question:
Which Wasp will land first?