在今天的节目中
我们将澄清关于新底盘的一些信息
公布疯狂周末活动
公布一些密码
坦克手们，大家好
周六，我们的新底盘出现在游戏中
当然，这引起了大家很多疑问
所以，我们决定对底盘的变化进行了一个小的分析
showing some not very obvious points and giving a
couple of tips.
First and most importantly, we have changed
the system of kill zones on maps.
This means that now you can be on the roofs
of buildings,
edges on the border of the map
and even fly over areas that were previously
inaccessible.
But remember that landing outside the map
leads to death.
All this will bring a new look at the familiar
game modes and maps.
The second point directly concerns the overdrive.
The hull jumps due to the jet engine on the
bottom.
Because of this, the tank is not just jumping
vertically,
but also takes your current velocity into account.
That is, if you activate the overdrive on
takeoff as you are driving,
you will fly much further.
In this case, you can activate the jump while
falling into an abyss and save your life.
Also, if you catch a nuclear energy box in
the flight,
you can double jump by activating your overdrive again while airborne.
In flight, the tank retains control even when
hit.
So you can not only make kills in the air,
but also on the ground.
Now, goldbox hunting with Hopper has been
taken to the next level.
Don't think it's an overpowered hull.
It's light, so it cannot take much damage.
It is slower than the other light hulls and
although it accelerates a bit faster,
it still can't escape from Wasp by jumping from a bomb.
But it does not matter, the most important
question is if you put a Wasp on top of Hopper,
will it still jump?
The discount weekend has already begun.
Today, we have a 25 percent discount in the
Shop;
tomorrow, the same discounts will be applied on Garage items, and on Sunday,
you will be able to upgrade your garage with a 25 percent discount
and speed the upgrade up for half the price.
During the discount weekend, we will have
boosted battle funds and experience.
We will also have a special offer in the Shop
that contains the Hopper hull, Heat and Cold Resistance augments, and 100 Ultra Containers.
Ultra Containers will be available during
the weekend;
don’t hesitate to buy a few because you know what might “jump” out of them.
We have recently released an update that brought
the auto-shooting mode
to the mobile version of the game.
The background of this update is not that
confusing.
During the last few years,
we have been actively
working on the mobile version of the game
and analysing the feedback we were receiving
from you.
The mobile controls were the main problem
for many of you.
By adding the auto-shooting mode,
we intended
to make it easier for you to control your tank
as it removes shooting from the equation
with this feature enabled.
However, after the update, some of you asked
us to have an option to disable this mode,
and that’s what we did.
Most of the complaints are about the Railgun
turret.
You thought that the auto shooting mode
would let you start charging your railgun even before you see an opponent.
And actually you can do this, but it must
be done manually.
Just simply double-tap on the screen.
For continuous shooting, you will have to
hold your finger on the screen after double-tapping.
Some turrets will still have the shooting
button.
Not that old one, but a new switch one.
When it’s on, this button will be holding
a finger on the screen for you.
This is much more comfortable
than the old
method of firing
with the button held on such turrets as Vulcan or Twins.
We will continue to follow your feedback
to make it as comfortable as possible for both new and old players.
We will hide special codes in the next episodes
of the V-LOG.
Your task is to find them and send them through
a form in the description.
Answers should be submitted to this form,
not in the comments.
The winner of this contest will receive
the fully upgraded Hopper Hull in the maximum modification available for the winner's rank,
200 000 crystals, and 30 containers.
Second place will receive the Crisis drone,
150 000 crystals, and 20 containers.
Third place will receive an animated paint
(except those available only in special bundles)
70,000 crystals, and 10 containers.
Anyone who placed between 4th and 13th will
each receive 5 containers
and 20 000 crystals each.
Look carefully and do not be distracted
because both speed and accuracy determine the winner of this contest.
The first code is already hidden somewhere
in this video, so good luck and get going!
Welcome back to Youtuber Digest, our weekly
selection of best TO videos created by players.
First, watch Jumper as he creates a goldbox
montage
entirely from our limited time event 'Hovering Railgun' mode.
Did you enjoy this event?
Second, watch Jay Tanki as he shares with
us some epic highlights from the XP/BP format.
Just a quick reminder, if you want your videos
to be featured in a V-LOG,
then submit your videos in the YouTuber wannabe form,
which can be found in the videos description.
As expected, the new format of TOF Dream Team
turned out to be very interesting
due to the possibility of using overdrives.
They presented completely new tactics on absolutely
all maps.
By the way, about them.
For the first time in eSports history, the
Sandbox MM map was added to the map pool,
and it became a real discovery of the tournament
- a change of leader, quick attacks, comebacks,
surprising tactics - everything can be seen
exactly there...
The group stages are behind us and we congratulate
the teams
and wish them the best of luck in the next round
because the playoff fights
are waiting for them!
You can watch all the most interesting battles
as well as participate in the giveaways
on the Tanki Online eSports channel.
Now over to some more eSports news; this time:
Blitz tournaments.
Blitz N23, which was held in the Hard format
and Blitz N24, which was in the Light format,
have ended recently.
24 teams participated in both of these tournaments,
and they were divided into three grids.
Meet the winners:
Team Pointers and Eternity
- leaders of the first grid, where clans of First and Second Leagues were battling for the prize,
Knockout and Hello Kitty, who never stop entertaining
us with excellent results for several Blitzes,
Aaaaaaand OutLawz and Vertical in the third
bracket.
Create a clan and participate in the Blitz
tournaments
- these are "fast" tournaments where you can win crystals, shot effects,
Premium and Tankoins by participating every week.
The anticipated MotS TRIO tournament with
the coveted Impulse paint as the main prize
is waiting for you!
If you have two or three comrades, who like
to play with Railgun,
form a team and register for the tournament!
You can still apply today!
Follow the link in the description and find
out all the details on our eSports portal
tankisport.com.
That’s all for this week.
As always, like the video, subscribe, hit
the notification bell,
and wait for some fresh news next week;
we will be announcing something
really cool.
See you later.
BYE!
Last time you had to guess which Mammoth with
activated overdrive would destroy Ares.
The correct answer is: E
Congratulations to the winners!
And here is the new question.
Which Wasp will survive?