In today’s episode, we will be wrapping
up the GAME.
We’ll also be kicking off a fresh new Ultra
Weekend and searching for the final code.
Hello, tankers.
Last Saturday was the fifth and final day
of our quest - The GAME.
We announced the winners on Tuesday, October
20th.
The grand prize went to the player Scorpion321
this year.
Congratulations; your prize is on the way!
The players Yarik and KINGS-HERE also placed
on the podium.
You can see all the winners on the Forum by
clicking on the link in the description.
This time we took the mistakes of the previous
GAME into account.
It was played only on the weekends.
We tried to maintain a balance of the difficulty
when creating the questions.
If you have any suggestions for the next version
of the GAME,
leave them in the comments under this V-LOG.
We will certainly read and take note of them.
The Ultra Weekend just started today.
All weekend long, you will enjoy the increased
battle funds and experience.
As usual, Coinboxes and Ultra Containers will
appear in the Shop.
You’ll also find a special offer there in
the Shop, which contains 100 000 crystals,
50 Ultra Containers, and Coinboxes, all at
a 30% discount.
In addition to this, there will be 5 new special
missions.
They will not only give you rewards,
but also plenty of bonus stars to finish the challenge faster.
A week ago, a lot of you were asking us: “Where
is the V-LOG?”.
We took a break from the weekly V-LOG episodes
last Friday.
Instead, we hosted a livestream where we answered
the questions you asked us on the forum.
Of course, we couldn’t answer all of them,
but many of the questions were duplicated,
so we made sure to answer these popular ones.
Anyway, the livestream lasted two hours, much
longer than a single episode of the V-LOG.
Not everyone was able to watch the whole livestream,
so if you missed something, now’s the perfect time to rewatch it.
However, before you leave to watch the livestream,
a quick reminder:
we’ve hidden the final secret code somewhere in this V-LOG.
If you find it,
remember to enter it in the special form linked in the description of this video.
Next week, we’ll conclude this contest
and tell you who the most attentive player was...
Two years has passed since the last edition
of the TOF Dream Team tournament,
but we brought it back for you in 2020!
Due to many changes in the game mechanics
over the years,
the tournament has changed quite a bit.
Brand new overdrives and hull augments have
been added; the mechanics of many turrets,
especially close combat turrets, have changed.
The tournament unleashed the maps in a new
way,
especially the oldest "Sandbox" in the new MM version.
The 8 best clans of the TOF Dream Team tournament
met in the Playoffs
and played a set of interesting and intense matches to determine the winner.
Control was a real surprise of this tournament,
because they beat Eternity in the 1/4 Stage and their another strong opponent, Revenge,
who only lost one match in the group stages.
After three maps and six rounds of the first
semi-final, the match resulted in a draw;
the teams went to play penalty rounds, where
Control was able to take the lead and win.
The second semifinal match, Team Pointers
vs.
LaWs, was also played on three maps.
Here, Mr.BaHbKa123 and his team, Team Pointers,
reached the final with ease.
Meanwhile, in the Lower Bracket, Eternity
was stronger than Can't Stop in the lower grid,
and CoolDown lost to Knockout.
Then, in the Lower Bracket Semi-Finals, Eternity
defeated LaWs,
and Knockout made another sensation by
winning against Revenge with a score of 3:2.
The most important matches still remained
In the pre-Finals, Eternity easily knocked out Knockout without problems,
guaranteeing themselves a place in the TOP 3.
In the Upper Bracket Finals, the clear favorite,
Team Pointers,
and the dark horse of the tournament, Control, faced off.
The match was quite close at the beginning,
but at some point,
Team Pointers were able to latch on to some positive momentum
and take the lead to win with a score of 6:3.
Control moved down to the Lower Bracket Finals,
where Eternity was waiting for them.
In the first two rounds on Barda, Eternity
took one of them in a close fight
and took a 1:0 lead.
Next up, they played several grueling matchups
on Bobruisk and Gubhaka,
and it was a close 3:2 game heading into the fourth map: Red
Alert.
Here, Eternity rallied and took both rounds,
earning themselves a spot in the Grand Finals against the widely feared clan Team Pointers.
Heading into the championship match, the heavy
favorites were Team Pointers.
At the very beginning of the tournament, this
particular team was expected to win the championship crown,
and as expected, they went through
the entire grid without a single defeat!
The match opened on Red Alert, where Eternity
performed brilliantly, winning one and tying the other,
starting themselves off with some
positive momentum.
Next up, Sandbox MM, a very unpredictable
map;
it was there that Team Pointers took large leads on many of their rivals during
the tournament.
Instead, Eternity took the initiative on the
map lightning fast
and left no chance for their rivals to catch up, let alone take the
lead, in both rounds.
It hit Team Pointers’ morale very hard and
as the match progressed, unfortunately,
they were only able to take one round on Bobruisk,
while Eternity grew increasingly stronger.
At the end of eight tough rounds,
Eternity brought home the TOF Dream title with a score of 4:1!
Congratulations to the winners.
We are waiting for the next tournaments!
Welcome back to Youtuber Digest,
our weekly selection of the best TO videos created by players.
First, watch Jordan Tanki as he shows off
some of his Railgun skills in various battles!
Second, watch Alfi as he creates a super well
edited goldbox montage!
A quick reminder: if you want to be featured
in a future episode of the V-LOG,
then share your videos in the YouTuber Wannabe form,
which can be found in the videos description.
That's all for this week.
Don't forget to like the video and hit the
bell to stay all caught up on our latest videos!
And by the way, we have a small spoiler for
you.
BOO!
Last time, you had to guess which Hopper would
explode on the mine.
The correct answer is: C
Congratulations to the winners!
And here is the next question:
In which Zone
will Ares be destroyed?